{"status":"Success","data":{"question_paper":[{"question_no":"1","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d32\u0d38\u0d47\u0d1a\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7c?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d28\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d26 ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 ","option4":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"2","question":"\u0d13\u0d7e \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d47\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24","option2":"\u0d2d\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7d ","option3":"\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d26\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"3","question":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d41\u0d28\u0d26\u0d40\u0d24\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d7d ","option2":"\u0d06\u0d7c.\u0d21\u0d3f.\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02","option4":"\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d4d\u200c\u0d28\u0d3f ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"4","question":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d2e \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d7a\u0d38\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7d ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"5","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d48\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d33\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46?\r\n","option1":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d32\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 ","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d35\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d3f ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"6","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d32\u0d38\u0d47\u0d1a\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f? ","option1":"\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d37\u0d3e \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d41\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"7","question":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d17\u0d7e \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02?","option1":"1520","option2":"1526","option3":"1536","option4":"1556","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"8","question":"1857 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ? ","option1":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d27\u0d57\u0d33","option2":"\u0d2c\u0d39\u0d26\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d37 I","option3":"\u0d2c\u0d39\u0d26\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d37 I I ","option4":"\u0d05\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d37\u0d3e ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"9","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36 \u0d36\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f? ","option1":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d21\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d","option3":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"10","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d28\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d1c \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d7b ? ","option1":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35 \u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b ","option2":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d \r\n","option3":"\u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \r\n","option4":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d26\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26 \u0d38\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"11","question":"\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d24\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f:","option1":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7d \r\n","option2":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24 \r\n","option3":"\u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4b \r\n","option4":"\u0d07\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32 ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"12","question":"2017 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d41. \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d. \u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7a \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d37 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n","option1":"\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2b\u0d47\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d7d \r\n","option2":"\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d7c \u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d7c \r\n","option3":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u200c\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15 \r\n","option4":"\u0d15\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d7a ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"13","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d57\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d7e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d02 \r\n","option2":"\u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \r\n","option3":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d02 \r\n","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d02 ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"14","question":"\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d30\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ? ","option1":"\u0d10.\u0d0e.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d40\u0d38\u0d7c","option2":"\u0d10.\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d40\u0d38\u0d7c","option3":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d07\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"15","question":"\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d47 \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02? ","option1":"\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d21\u0d7d\u0d39\u0d3f","option2":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48","option4":"\u0d21\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d21\u0d42\u0d7a\r\n","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"16","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d47\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d7b ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d15\u0d7b \r\n","option2":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \r\n","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d7b \r\n","option4":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38 \u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d7b ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"17","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d21\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d48\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \r\n","option3":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f ","option4":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d23\u0d02 ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"18","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d27\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24 ?","option1":"NH 47","option2":"NH 49","option3":"NH 44","option4":"NH 17","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"19","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ? \r\n","option1":"\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17 ","option2":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d\u200c ","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7a\u0d21\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"20","question":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c \r\n","option2":"\u0d05\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d28\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \r\n","option3":"\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d2e\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \r\n","option4":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d46\u0d7b ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"21","question":"\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d23\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ?","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d26\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"22","question":"2024 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n\r\n","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b \r\n","option3":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d7d\u0d38\u0d4d \r\n","option4":"\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4b ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"23","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d30 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","option1":"1","option2":"2","option3":"3","option4":"4","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"24","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 [\u0d2a\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \r\n","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \r\n","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 \r\n","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02 ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"25","question":"\u0d2a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d48 \r\n","option2":"\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c \r\n","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d48 \r\n","option4":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"26","question":"\u0d26\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d06\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d02 \r\n","option2":"\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02 \r\n","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d41-\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7c \r\n","option4":"\u0d05\u0d30\u0d41\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"27","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40. \u0d35\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d41 ?\r\n","option1":"11","option2":"12","option3":"13","option4":"14","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"28","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d32\u0d02?\r\n","option1":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d\u200c ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d\u200c ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d17\u0d30\u0d02 ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"29","question":"\u0d2c\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30 ","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c \r\n","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d18\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"30","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \"\u0d05\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24 \"?","option1":"\u0d15\u0d30\u0d38\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3e ","option2":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d47\u0d28 ","option3":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d47\u0d28 ","option4":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d47\u0d28 ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"31","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d16\u0d4d\u200c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7b \r\n","option2":"\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c \r\n","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7c \r\n","option4":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"32","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 ?","option1":"3","option2":"5","option3":"6","option4":"8","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"33","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02 ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d42\u0d7a 8 \r\n","option2":"\u0d1c\u0d42\u0d32\u0d48 21 \r\n","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 22 \r\n","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d 23 ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"34","question":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d47\u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d40\u0d36\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d :\r\n","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4b \u0d37\u0d35\u0d7c \r\n","option2":"\u0d32\u0d42 \r\n","option3":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d16 \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d16\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d42\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"35","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46?","option1":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28 ","option2":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b ","option3":"\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d40\u0d2a\u0d4d ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"36","question":"\u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d47 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d31\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d35\u0d47 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d2e\u0d3e \r\n","option2":"\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \r\n","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d47\u0d35 \r\n","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35 \u0d2f\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d28 ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"37","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u200c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d25\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d \r\n","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d \r\n","option3":"\u0d2c\u0d40\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7c \r\n","option4":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"38","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d46\u0d30\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d , \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d02\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28 ?\r\n\r\n","option1":"\u0d05\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option2":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d21 \r\n","option3":"\u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f \r\n","option4":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"39","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d27\u0d28 \u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4b \u0d05\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d4b \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u200c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f \r\n","option2":"\u0d09\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f \r\n","option3":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c \r\n","option4":"\u0d27\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"40","question":"\u0d13\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d17\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d7c \r\n","option2":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \r\n","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \r\n","option4":"\u0d1a\u0d40\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d31\u0d3f ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"41","question":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d17\u0d02\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d30\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d \r\n","option2":"\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d16\u0d32\u0d46 \r\n","option3":"\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3e \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d35\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d1c\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d21\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42. \u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d7c\u0d1c\u0d3f ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"42","question":"\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d37\u0d46\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d09\u0d7e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n","option1":"11","option2":"10","option3":"9","option4":"8","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"43","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d26\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?\r\n","option1":"\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d4d\u200c\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \r\n","option2":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d02 ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15 ","option4":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"44","question":"\u0d27\u0d28\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ","option2":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u200c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f \r\n","option3":"\u0d09\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"45","question":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f ","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d23\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \r\n","option3":"\u0d2b\u0d46\u0d21\u0d31\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \r\n","option4":"\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"46","question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7a\u0d35\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d39\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d21\u0d4d\u200c\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e?\r\n","option1":"\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \r\n","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d1c\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \r\n","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d7b \r\n","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"47","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d47 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d38\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d02 ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d30 ","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32 \r\n","option3":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d ","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d02 ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"48","question":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d23\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d24\u0d43\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d38\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b \r\n","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d46. \u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7b \r\n","option3":"\u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41 ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"49","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d27\u0d28\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d1f\u0d3f. \u0d35\u0d3f. \u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d \r\n","option2":"\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f.\u0d0e.\u0d2e\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d26\u0d4d \r\n","option3":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d06\u0d7c. \u0d17\u0d57\u0d30\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d7b ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"50","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d7a?\r\n","option1":"\u0d0e\u0d02. \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d02 \r\n","option2":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d24\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \r\n","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d46.\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d09\u0d37 \r\n","option4":"\u0d1c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d2b\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2e \u0d2c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"51","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d36\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d57\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d26 \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d42\u0d7c \r\n","option2":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d15\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7d ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"52","question":"\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d17 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \r\n","option2":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \r\n","option3":"\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \r\n","option4":"\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"53","question":"\u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u200c\u0d31\u0d41 \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d7d ?\r\n","option1":"\u0d35\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \r\n","option2":"\u0d05\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d1f ","option4":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02\u0d15\u0d41\u0d33\u0d02 ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"54","question":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n","option1":"\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7a \r\n","option2":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f \r\n","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7b \r\n","option4":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d21 ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"55","question":"\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d32\u0d39\u0d33\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d?\r\n","option1":"\u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b\u200c\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f \r\n","option2":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23 \u0d17\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41 \r\n","option3":"\u0d1a\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \r\n","option4":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d15\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"56","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f GST \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n\r\n","option1":"\u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \r\n","option2":"\u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d ","option3":"\u0d1c\u0d7c\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"57","question":"'\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d7d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\r\n","option1":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d32\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15 \r\n","option2":"\u0d05\u0d2b\u0d4d\u200c\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7b \r\n","option3":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d7b \r\n","option4":"\u0d28\u0d47\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7e ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"58","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d7c\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f?\r\n","option1":"\u0d1c\u0d35\u0d39\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d46\u0d39\u0d4d\u200c\u0d31\u0d41 \r\n","option2":"\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d39\u0d26\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d36\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f \r\n","option3":"\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d2e\u0d7b\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d39\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d \r\n","option4":"\u0d28\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d3f ","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"59","question":"\u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d18\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d0f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d09\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f?\r\n","option1":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f \r\n","option2":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d17\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d05\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d32 ","option4":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d32\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d7c ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"60","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d17\u0d40\u0d38\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d48\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d?\r\n","option1":"\u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d4d \r\n","option2":"\u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d30 \r\n","option3":"\u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d42 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d7c \r\n","option4":"\u0d13\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"61","question":"The word nearest in meaning to the word 'Alert' is","option1":"energetic","option2":"observant","option3":"watchful","option4":"intelligent","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"62","question":"Which of the following is the word opposite in meaning to the word 'Assemble'?","option1":"dispose","option2":"disperse","option3":"dispense","option4":"displace","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"63","question":"Choose the incorrectly spelt word:","option1":"Accommodate","option2":"Accumulate","option3":"Recommend","option4":"Vaccation","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"64","question":"Find out the correct sentence:","option1":"Each of the boy are clever","option2":"Each of the boys were clever","option3":"Each of the boys is clever","option4":"Each of the boys have clever","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"65","question":"\"He plays piano\" is an example of:","option1":"imperative sentence","option2":"interrogative sentence","option3":"declarative sentence","option4":"exclamatory sentence","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"66","question":"The baby walked slowly. In this sentence 'slowly' is:","option1":"adjective","option2":"adverb","option3":"pronoun","option4":"noun","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"67","question":"Passive voice of \"He has drawn two pictures\" is","option1":"Two pictures have been drawn by him","option2":"Two pictures has been drawn by him","option3":"Two pictures had been drawn by him","option4":"Two pictures had being drawn by him","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"68","question":"The reported speech of \"Mary said, I am watching television\" is:","option1":"Mary said that she is watching television","option2":"Mary said that she has been watching television","option3":"Mary said that she watches television","option4":"Mary said that she was watching television","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"69","question":"Pick out the singular form from the given words:","option1":"Data","option2":"Mice","option3":"Teeth","option4":"Fungus","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"70","question":"Which of the following is a one word of \"A government by a King or a Queen\"?","option1":"Monarchy","option2":"Autocracy","option3":"Aristocracy","option4":"Democracy","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"71","question":"Neither his brother nor his sister_____ wise.","option1":"are","option2":"were","option3":"has","option4":"is","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"72","question":"The empty mountain regions without trees are an awful:","option1":"site","option2":"sight","option3":"cite","option4":"seen","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"73","question":"Replace the word in bold letters with the right phrase chosen from those given below: Abraham Lincoln wanted to ABOLISH slavery in USA.","option1":"put and end to","option2":"put up with","option3":"put on","option4":"put up","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"74","question":"Gifty is ______ than Geetha.","option1":"young","option2":"youngest","option3":"younger","option4":"eldest","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"75","question":"We expect _____ official enquiry into the incident.","option1":"the","option2":"an","option3":"a","option4":"some","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"76","question":"Chithra dances well _____ ?","option1":"does she?","option2":"doesn't she?","option3":"did she?","option4":"didn't she?","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"77","question":"Rani is holding a vase ______ her hand.","option1":"on","option2":"under","option3":"upon","option4":"in","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"78","question":"Children ______ to school every day.","option1":"go","option2":"goes","option3":"going","option4":"went","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"79","question":"Shakespeare is the _____ Dramatist in English.","option1":"great","option2":"greater","option3":"greatest","option4":"more greath","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"80","question":"He has been speaking continuously _____ 5'O clock.","option1":"since","option2":"for","option3":"from","option4":"to","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"81","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d2e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d42\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d42\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d07\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d23\u0d33\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30?\r\n","option1":"90","option2":"105","option3":"120","option4":"160","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"82","question":"441:462::841:x \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7d x \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30?","option1":"800","option2":"830","option3":"860","option4":"870","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"83","question":"\u0d05\u0d7b\u0d37\u0d3e \u0d35\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 3 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d 4 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d. \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d47\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30?","option1":"5","option2":"7","option3":"3.5","option4":"12","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"84","question":"# \u0d17\u0d41\u0d23\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 @ \u0d39\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 * \u0d38\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d32\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 % \u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d15\u0d32\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d42\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d7d 16@2*3#4%10 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30?","option1":"34","option2":"4","option3":"-2","option4":"10","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"85","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"57","option2":"59","option3":"61","option4":"67","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"86","question":"62,55.48, ........ \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"0","option2":"1","option3":"-1","option4":"-2","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"87","question":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d2c\u0d48\u0d7d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f 15,000 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7a 15% \u0d28\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41. \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d34\u0d2f \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"12,000","option2":"12,750","option3":"2,250","option4":"12,500","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"88","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d0e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4d 8.2 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d. \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"1.025","option2":"1.250","option3":"65.006","option4":"64.016","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"89","question":"\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f 125 \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d. \u0d07\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d12\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f 118 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d12\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?","option1":"1062","option2":"7","option3":"118","option4":"188","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"90","question":"\u0d05\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7b 300 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f 40 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d47\u0d17\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2c\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41.\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d30\u0d3f 50 \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d7c \u0d35\u0d47\u0d17\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d07\u0d24\u0d47 \u0d26\u0d42\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d02?","option1":"75 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ","option2":"90 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ","option3":"60 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ","option4":"80 \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d ","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"91","question":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d7c \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d7c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02?","option1":"2","option2":"4","option3":"6","option4":"8","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"92","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 15% \u0d06\u0d23\u0d4d 900?","option1":"135","option2":"13500","option3":"60000","option4":"6000","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"93","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d40\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d40\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02?\r\n","option1":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \r\n","option2":"\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02 \r\n","option3":"\u0d30\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d1f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 \r\n","option4":"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02 ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"94","question":"15:18=x:144 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7d x \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30?","option1":"60","option2":"72","option3":"90","option4":"120","answer":"4"},{"question_no":"95","question":"2008 \u0d32\u0d46 \u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d36\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02?\r\n","option1":"\u0d2c\u0d41\u0d27\u0d7b \r\n","option2":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d02 \r\n","option3":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d36\u0d28\u0d3f ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"96","question":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d42\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d7d\u0d26\u0d4b \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41. \u0d07\u0d35\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d7b\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d47 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2e\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d. \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d08 \u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","option1":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e \r\n","option2":"\u0d38\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d26\u0d30\u0d3f ","option3":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d3f \r\n","option4":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f ","answer":"2"},{"question_no":"97","question":"15,20,26,33,41,.....\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d46\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d16\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02?","option1":"50","option2":"49","option3":"52","option4":"57","answer":"1"},{"question_no":"98","question":"BREAK \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d ASDBJ \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d7d SOLAR \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d02?","option1":"RPKBS","option2":"TPMBS","option3":"RPKBQ","option4":"TPKBQ","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"99","question":"\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d46\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","option1":"1000","option2":"8000","option3":"16000","option4":"27000","answer":"3"},{"question_no":"100","question":"\u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d41 1500 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d3f 1320 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d41. \u0d0e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d28\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d36\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02?","option1":"10%","option2":"12%","option3":"14%","option4":"16%","answer":"2"}]},"code":"100"}